ROBERT MURPHY

PROFILE

I am a professional full-stack developer (web and mobile) with 7+ years of working experience.

I enjoy the diversity and challenges that I meet every project. It keeps me into learning new things that I like most in this profession.

I am the kind of person who wants to dig deep into your goal/need/problems and get you the solution in a timely manner with the highest standards. My clients say I'm quite fast at understanding their needs. Here are some technologies I have working experience.

- * FrontEnd: React, Vue, JavaScript, ES6, jQuery, HTML5, CSS, Sass, PSD to HTML, etc..
- * UI Framework: Bootstrap, Material Design ,AntD.
- * Backend: NodeJS, Express, PHP, Laravel, RESTfull API.
- * Database: MongoDB, MySQL.

I love my work and always try to follow the best practices. I can assure you maximum availability and error-free semantic code.

So let's get started:)

Thank you

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FrontEnd/Automation developer at Tiki team, Remote

July 2014 — November 2018

Tested Unit and updated application modules

- Tested Tiki FrontEnd development
- Updated and optimized core library
- Development of Web Scraping and Automation using Python.

Front-End Developer Tom O'callaghan, Cork

July 2019 — July 2021

Development of frontend using javascrpt framework.

- Used Vue,Laravel to build UI.
- Used React/Next to UI.
- Built UX/UI using Next.js, Tailwind CSS.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, University of Ottawa

 ${\it September 2009-April 2013}$